swellpath.com 2011-12-08

# Privacy Policy | SwellPath Interactive

Thank you for visiting SwellPath.com. This SwellPath Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you access our site.

## Information Collection and Use

SwellPath receives limited “personally identifiable information,” including your IP address. SwellPath also collects names, email address, and mailing addresses (including street, city, state, and zip code) from users that wish to provide that information through our contact forms. We use this personally identifiable information as follows:

SwellPath requires that you provide your email address on the contact us section of the Site so that we are able to respond to your question(s) by email. You have the option of also providing your name, company name, and other information.

SwellPath also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP Address and the page you requested. Your IP address is not linked to your email address or SwellPath.

SwellPath also collects email addresses for users who wish to sign up for our email newsletters. SwellPath will not sell or rent your email address, name, mailing address, or other supplied information to anyone. SwellPath will not share your email address, first or last name, mailing address, or other received information to anyone, except as stated below:

We may disclose personally identifiable information about you as legally required in order for us to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes.

SwellPath receives your IP address each time you view a Web page from the Site. Your IP address may be used for various purposes, including:

To diagnose service or technology problems reported by you that are associated with your IP address.  
To estimate the total number of users visiting the Site from specific locales, countries or regions of the world.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes a unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a Web site’s computers and then stored on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie cannot obtain information from your hard drive, destroy files, or transmit viruses. You do not need to accept cookies in order to use SwellPath’s website.

Each website can send its own cookie to your browser, if your browser’s preferences allow it. To protect your privacy, your browser normally only permits a website to access cookies that it has previously sent to you, but not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

## Removal of Information

If you request deletion of your email address or any other identifiable information, your information will be deactivated and removed from our databases within 30 days.

## Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, send an email to info@swellpath.com. Thanks again for visiting SwellPath.
